<resources>
    <string name="app_name">C&amp;C:Online Spymaster</string>


    <string name="title_section1">Players</string>
    <string name="title_section2">Open Lobbies</string>
    <string name="title_section3">In Game</string>



    <string name="KanesWrath">Kane\'s Wrath</string>
    <string name="CandC3">C&amp;C 3</string>
    <string name="Generals">Generals</string>
    <string name="ZeroHour">Zero Hour</string>
    <string name="RedAlert3">Red Alert 3</string>

    <string name="KanesWrathJSON">cnc3kw</string>
    <string name="CandC3JSON">cnc3</string>
    <string name="GeneralsJSON">generals</string>
    <string name="ZeroHourJSON">generalszh</string>
    <string name="RedAlert3JSON">ra3</string>

    <string name="connection_error">Connection Error</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>


    <string name="licence">Licence</string>
    <string name="BSD">Copyright © 2015, Henry Zimmerman\n
            All rights reserved.\n\n

            Redistribution and use in source and binary forms, with or without
            modification, are permitted provided that the following conditions are met:\n\n

            Redistributions of source code must retain the above copyright notice, this
            list of conditions and the following disclaimer.\n\n

            Redistributions in binary form must reproduce the above copyright notice,
            this list of conditions and the following disclaimer in the documentation
            and/or other materials provided with the distribution.\n\n

            Neither the name of C-C-Online-Spymaster nor the names of its
            contributors may be used to endorse or promote products derived from
            this software without specific prior written permission.\n\n


            THIS SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED BY THE COPYRIGHT HOLDERS AND CONTRIBUTORS "AS IS"
            AND ANY EXPRESS OR IMPLIED WARRANTIES, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, THE
            IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE ARE
            DISCLAIMED. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE COPYRIGHT HOLDER OR CONTRIBUTORS BE LIABLE
            FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, EXEMPLARY, OR CONSEQUENTIAL
            DAMAGES (INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, PROCUREMENT OF SUBSTITUTE GOODS OR
            SERVICES; LOSS OF USE, DATA, OR PROFITS; OR BUSINESS INTERRUPTION) HOWEVER
            CAUSED AND ON ANY THEORY OF LIABILITY, WHETHER IN CONTRACT, STRICT LIABILITY,
            OR TORT (INCLUDING NEGLIGENCE OR OTHERWISE) ARISING IN ANY WAY OUT OF THE USE
            OF THIS SOFTWARE, EVEN IF ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGE.</string>

    <string name="AndroidAssetStudio">
        All art that was not provided by the Android SDK was generated by Android Asset Studio.
        All art generated by the Android Asset Studio is licensed under a \n
        Creative Commons Attribution 3.0 Unported License.
    </string>
    <string name="map">Map:</string>
    <string name="players">Players:</string>
    <string name="the_game_is_locked">The game is locked</string>

    <string name="ok">OK</string>
    <string name="settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="nickname">Nickname:</string>
    <string name="id">ID:</string>
    <string name="pid">PID:</string>
    <string name="receive_notifications">Receive Notifications</string>
    <string name="friends">Friends</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="player_is_you">Player is You</string>
    <string name="reset_db_disclaimer">
        "This will reset the database that holds all of the players that you have marked as your friend, for you to receive notifications about their online status, and those you marked as yourself.

        Are you sure you want to continue?
        "</string>
    <string name="reset_db_summary">Reset the local database that holds player data.</string>

    <!--Strings for tagging and retrieving preferences-->
    <string name="licence_pref">license_preference</string>
    <string name="notify_if_online_pref">notify_if_online</string>
    <string name="receive_notifications_pref">receive_notifications</string>
    <string name="time_interval_pref">time_interval</string>
    <string name="manage_friends_pref">manage_friends</string>
    <string name="reset_db_pref">reset_db</string>
    <string name="reset_player_db">Reset Player Database</string>
    <!-- END Strings for tagging and retrieving preferences-->



</resources>
